[TV PLAYING]
(Howard:)Hey, Leonard,
where do you come down on giant ants?
(Raj:)Sheldon says impossible,
Howard and I say not only possible...
(Raj:)...but as a mode of transportation,
way cooler than the Batmobile.
(Sheldon:)You are ignoring the square-cube law.
(Sheldon:)The giant ant would be crushed
under the weight of its exoskeleton.
(Sheldon:)For the record, the appropriate ranking
of cool modes of transportation...
...is jetpack, hover board, transporter,
Batmobile and then giant ant.
Seriously, you have nothing better
to do than sit around...
(Leonard:)...and discuss the possibility
of giant ants?
(Howard:)-What's with him?
-Perhaps he's at a sensitive point...
(Sheldon:)...in his monthly cycle.
(Howard:)Are you saying he's man-struating?
(Sheldon:)Not literally.
(Sheldon:)But as far back as the 17th century...